Anna Hyatt Huntington Papers
Anna Hyatt Huntington Papers
- Correspondence-subject files
  - National Institute of Arts and Letters (Box 48)
    See also Butler, Nicholas Murray (Box 15) and Train, Arthur (Box 56).
  - National Sculpture Society, includes photograph of 75th anniversary medal (Lo Medico and Grigor) (Box 48)
  - National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception (Box 48)
  - National Woman's Party, See Greenbie, Marjorie Latta Barstow (Box 33).
  - Natural Science for Youth Foundation, See Forbes, John Ripley (Box 32).
  - Nebel, Berthold and Erwin (Box 48)
  - Nelson, Jack Jerry, includes original artwork, photographs (Box 48)
  - Nevill, Richard (Lord) (Box 48)
  - Neville Public Museum (Green Bay, Wis.) (Box 48)
  - New Jersey State Museum (Box 48)
  - New York (City) (Box 48)
  - New York (State) (Box 48)
  - New York Botanical Gardens (Box 48)
  - New York Department of Parks, re Marti statue (Box 48)
  - New-York Historical Society (Box 49)
  - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad Company (Box 49)
  - New York Numismatic Club (Box 49)
  - New York State College of Forestry at Syracuse University, See Syracuse University (Box 54).
  - New York State Teachers College, Cortland (Box 49)
  - New York-Tokyo Sister-City Affiliation (Box 49)
  - New York University (Box 49)
  - New York Yacht Club (Box 49)
  - New York Zoological Society (Box 49)
  - Newell, Edward T., See American Numismatic Society (Box 9).
  - Newman, Paul (Box 49)
  - Newport News Land Corporation (Box 49)
  - Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company, 2 folders (Box 49)
  - Nichols, Hobart, See National Academy of Design (Box 48).
  - Nickerson, Ruth (Box 49)
  - Niehaus, Marie J. (daughter of Charles Henry Niehaus) (Box 49)
  - Noe, Bessie Wherry (Box 49)
  - Noel, John Vavasour (Box 49)
  - Norfolk Museum (Box 49)
  - Norris, Henry (Box 49)
  - Northwestern University (Box 49)
  - Norton, Elizabeth, includes original art (Box 49)
  - Norton, Nancy R., includes original art, poetry (Box 49)
  - Nye, Frank W. (Box 49)
  - Nykl, A. R. (Box 49)
  - N (Box 49)
  - Old Dartmouth Historical Society (Box 50)
  - Oppenheim, Max Freiherr von (Box 50)
  - Organization of American States, See Pan American Union (Box 50).
  - Osborn, Fairfield, See New York Zoological Society (Box 49).
  - Osborn, Henry Fairfield, See American Museum of Natural History (Box 8).
  - Oursler, Grace (Mrs. Fulton) (Box 50)
  - O (Box 50)
  - Packman, Arthur (Box 50)
  - Paddock, Josephine (Box 50)
  - Paeff, Bashka (Box 50)
  - Palisades Interstate Park Commission (Box 50)
  - Palmer, Courtlandt (Box 50)
  - [General William Jackson] Palmer Memorial Association (Colorado Springs, Colo.) (Box 50)
  - Pan American Society (Box 50)
  - Pan American Union (Box 50)
  - Park, Madeleine (Box 50)
  - Parker, William Belmont, See Hispanic Society of America (Boxes 35-37).
  - Parrish Art Museum (Box 50)
  - Paxton, Elizabeth O. (Box 50)
  - Peers, E. Allison (Box 50)
  - Peixotto, George (Box 50)
  - Pell, Stephen H. P. and Sarah (Box 50)
    See also Fort Ticonderoga Museum (Box 32).
  - Pellowe, Edward, letter and newspaper clippings about Huntington (Box 50)
    Gift of Kiersten Gawronski, 2021
  - Peninsula Chamber of Commerce (Box 50)
  - Pennell, Joseph (Box 50)
  - Penney, Clara (Box 50)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts (Box 50)
  - Perkins, Abbie M., 1923-1959; undated; includes photograph; 2 folders (Box 50)
  - Perkins, Clara Leonora Huntington, Henry E. Huntington's daughter (Box 50)
  - Perry, George C. (Box 50)
  - Pershing, John J. (Box 50)
  - Phelps, William Lyon (Box 50)
  - Phoenix Art Museum (Box 50)
  - Pickett, Grace, See Art files: Picket, Grace E. (Box 3).
  - Pierpont Morgan Library (Box 51)
  - Pijoan, Joseph (Box 51)
  - Pippenger, Robert (Box 51)
  - Plimpton, Edith H., includes photographs (Box 51)
  - Poland, Reginald (Box 51)
    See also Atlanta Art Association (Box 9).
  - Polašek, Albin (Box 51)
  - Pollock, John (Box 51)
  - Pomeroy, Lucy (Box 51)
  - Pope, Arthur Upham, See Asia Institute (Box 9).
  - Pope, John Russell (Box 51)
  - Porter, John and Marie (Box 51)
  - Potter, J. B. (Box 51)
  - Prezzi, Wilma (Box 51)
  - Price, Frederic Newlin (Box 51)
  - Price, Henry Brooks (Box 51)
  - Prince, J. Dyneley and Addie (Box 51)
  - Purdue, Maude E. (Box 51)
  - Putnam, Brenda, includes original art, sketches (Box 51)
  - Putnam, Herbert (Box 51)
  - P (Box 51)
  - Quattlesaum, Paul (Box 51)
  - Queen's College, 2 folders (Box 51)
  - Quesada y Miranda, Gonzalo de (Box 52)
  - Racine Art Association (Box 52)
  - Randall-MacIver, David (Box 52)
  - Real Academia de Belles Artes de San Jorge (Box 52)
  - Red Cross, National (Box 52)
  - Red Cross, Sunset Hill (Box 52)
  - Regional Museum of Spartanburg County, South Carolina (Box 52)
  - Reid, Charles Gordon (Box 52)
  - Reilly, Frank (Box 52)
  - Research and Security Corporation (Box 52)
  - Riano, Juan, See Spanish Embassy (Box 54).
  - Rice, Alexander Hamilton (Box 52)
  - Richard, Betti (Box 52)
  - Rivera, Diego (Box 52)
  - Robertson, William Spence (Box 52)
  - Robinson, Corinne Roosevelt (Box 52)
  - Robinson, Edwin Arlington (Box 52)
  - Rochovansky, John (Box 52)
  - Rockefeller, John D. (Box 52)
  - Rodriguez Marin, Francisco (Box 52)
  - Roller, Marion Bender (Box 52)
  - Romero, Cesar (Box 52)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Box 52)
  - Rose, Edward Douglas and Susan, includes photograph (Box 52)
  - Ross, Walter G. (Box 52)
  - Royere, Jean (Box 52)
    See also Printed material: Books: About AHH: Royere, Jean / Le Musicisme Sculptural (Box 104) and Writings of others: Royere, Jean (Box 121).
  - Rudin, Paul (Box 52)
  - Rushmore, Arthur (Box 52)
  - Rutledge, Archibald (Box 52)
  - R, 2 folders (Box 52)
  - Sabatini, Raphael (Box 53)
  - Saginaw Museum (Box 53)
  - St. Augustine (Fla.) ("Queen Isabella") (Box 53)
  - St. Gaudens Memorial (Box 53)
  - St. John's Riverside Hospital (Yonkers, N.Y.) (Box 53)
  - Saltus, J. Sanford (Box 53)
  - Sanchez Canton, Francisco Javier (Box 53)
  - Sanchez-Toda, Jose Luis (Box 53)
  - [Birgen] Sandzen Memorial Gallery (Lindsborg, Kansas) (Box 53)
  - Sanford, Edward Field (Box 53)
  - Sarton, George (Box 53)
  - Satterlee, Herbert L. (Box 53)
  - Schaub-Koch, Emile, 1930-1939; 1944-1965,; undated; includes photographs in last folder; 6 folders (Box 53)
    See also Printed material: Books about AHH (Box 104) and Writings (by others): Schaub-Koch, Emile (Boxes 121 and 122)
  - Schmidt, I. W. (Box 53)
  - Schomberg, Bertram (Box 53)
  - Schroeder, H. L. (Box 53)
  - Scott, Harry Burgoyne and Julia, includes photographs (Box 53)
  - Scottish Deerhound Club of America, See Deerhounds: Scottish Deerhound Club of America (Box 29)/
  - Scudder, Janet (Box 53)
  - Sears, Philip S. (Box 53)
  - Sheldon, Jennie A. (Mrs. George) (Box 53)
  - Sherrill, Charles Hitchcock (Box 53)
  - Shrady, Frederick Charles (Box 53)
  - Siau, Nell (Box 53)
  - Sigma Delta Pi (Box 53)
  - Smith, Carleton, See National Arts Foundation (Box 48).
  - Smith, Ismael (Box 53)
  - Smith, Martha (Mrs. J. Yeardley), Harriet Hyatt Mayor's granddaughter (Box 53)
  - Smith, Robinson (Box 53)
  - Smithsonian Institution (Box 53)
  - Snider, Helen, See Hayward/Huntington/IBM Mediterranean exhibit (Box 35).
  - Society of Animal Artists (Box 53)
  - Society of Medallists (Box 54)
  - Sorolla, Joaquin (Box 54)
  - South Carolina State Commission of Forestry (Box 54)
  - Southwest Museum, See Hodge, Frederick W. (Box 37).
  - Southwest Texas State Teachers College (Box 54)
  - Spaeth, Carola (Box 54)
  - Spanish Consulate (Box 54)
  - Spanish Embassy (Box 54)
  - Spanish Institute, Inc. (Box 54)
  - Spalding, Keith (Box 54)
  - Speyer, James (Box 54)
  - Spicer-Simpson, Theodore (Mrs.) (Box 54)
  - Sportfolio (Box 54)
  - Spreckels, Alma de Bretteville (Box 54)
  - Springweiler, Erwin (Box 54)
  - Squillini, Joseph (Box 54)
  - Stanerigg Farm, 2 folders (Box 54)
  - Stanerigg Kennels, See Deerhounds (Boxes 19-30)
  - Stanfield, Marion Baar (Box 54)
  - Starkweather, William (Box 54)
  - Steele High School Alumni Association, See Dayton Art Institute (Box 18).
  - Sterner, Albert (Box 54)
  - Stettinius, Joseph (Box 54)
  - Stevens Institute of Technology (Hoboken, N.J.) (Box 54)
  - Stevenson, Edward Luther (Box 54)
  - Stewart, Marie (Box 54)
  - Stick, Frank (Box 54)
  - Stokes, Frank Wilbert (Box 54)
  - Stucki, M. (Box 54)
  - Students (Box 54)
  - Swarz, Sahl (Box 54)
  - [Sheldon] Swope Art Gallery (Box 54)
  - Sympathy telegrams (copies), re death of Archer Milton Huntington (Box 54)
  - Syracuse University, includes handwritten text of speech (Box 54)
  - S, 2 folders (Box 55)
  - Tams & King (Box 55)
  - Tarbox, F. G. and Gurdon L. (son), See Brookgreen Gardens: General (Boxes 11-13).
  - Taulbee, Dan, includes original art, numerous illustrated letters and cards (Box 55)
  - Textile Museum, See Myers, George Hewitt (Box 47).
  - Thiessen, Alice (Box 55)
  - Thomas, Henry (Box 55)
  - Tinker, Edward Larocque (Box 55)
  - Tittle, Walter (Box 55)
  - Townsend, Emily (Box 55)
  - Townsend, Katherine Mayor Cook and C. Blake, AHH's niece and her husband (Box 55)
  - Townsend, Lawrence ("Laurie") (Box 55)
  - Townsend, Natalie (Mrs. Lawrence)
    - 1932-1959 (Box 55)
    - Undated, includes photographs (Box 56)
  - Train, Arthur (Box 56)
  - Travers Detective Agency (Box 56)
  - Troubetzkoy, Pierre (Box 56)
  - Trowbridge, Alexander B. (Box 56)
  - Turnure, Percy R. (Box 56)
  - Tweed, Harrison, See Fogg Art Museum (Box 32).
  - T (Box 56)
  - Union de Mujeres Americanas, Inc. (Box 56)
  - United States Congress (Box 56)
  - United States Department of State (Box 56)
  - United States Treasury Department (Box 56)
  - University of Bridgeport (Box 56)
  - University of North Carolina (Box 56)
  - University of South Carolina (Box 56)
    See also Memorabilia: Miscellaneous: University of South Carolina (Oversize 2).
  - University of Texas (Box 56)
  - U (Box 56)
  - Van Dyke, Henry (Box 56)
  - Van Kirk, Florence M. P. (Box 56)
  - Van Pelt, John V. (Box 56)
  - Vanamee, Grace D. (Mrs. William), See American Academy of Arts and Letters (Boxes 7 and 8).
  - Vanderbilt, Harold S. (Box 56)
  - Vega-Inclan, Benigno (Box 56)
  - Viladrich, Miguel (Box 56)
  - Vinal, Harold (Box 56)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (Box 56)
  - Vivekananda, Swami, See Burke, Marie Louise (Box 15).
  - Voices, See Vinal, Harold (Box 56).
  - Vonnoh, Robert William (Mrs.) (Box 56)
  - Vose, Robert C. (Box 56)
  - Vozech, Anthony (Box 56)
  - V (Box 56)
  - Wacksmuth, Henry (Box 56)
  - Waddell, Maude (Box 56)
  - Wadsworth Atheneum (Hartford, Conn.) (Box 57)
  - Wallace, Grace, includes original poetry (Box 57)
  - Warren, E. "Witty", includes original poetry (Box 57)
  - Washington Cathedral (Box 57)
  - Washington County Museum of Fine Arts (Hagerstown, Md.) (Box 57)
  - Watrous, Harry W. (Box 57)
  - Watson, Dudley Crafts (Box 57)
  - Watts, Harriet Mayor (Box 57)
  - Waxman, Samuel M. and Bashka, See Paeff, Bashka (Box 50).
  - Weems, Katherine Lane and Carrington (Box 57)
    See also Brookgreen Gardens: General (Boxes 11-13) and Photographs: Artwork by others: Lane, Katherine (Box 93).
  - Weill, Erna (Box 57)
  - Wein, Albert W. (Box 57)
  - Weinman, Adolph Alexander (Box 57)
  - Weinman, Robert A. (Box 57)
  - Wellesley College (Box 57)
  - Werboff, Michael (Box 57)
  - Wesley, —, includes original poetry (Box 57)
  - West, Levon (Box 57)
  - West, Louis Caulton, See American Numismatic Society (Box 9).
  - Wheeler, George B. (Box 57)
  - Whitaker, Frederic, includes typescript, "The Supreme Test of Civilization" (Box 57)
  - White Motor Company (Box 57)
  - Whitelaw, Robert N. S., See Mechlin, Leila (Box 46). (Box 57)
  - Whitener, Paul W., See Hickory Museum of Art (Box 35).
  - Whitmore, Frederick, includes original poetry (Box 57)
  - Who's Who in America (Box 57)
  - Wiley, Louis (Box 57)
  - Williams, Roger (Captain) (Box 57)
    Hispanic Society of America (Boxes 35-37)
    Mariners' Museum (Newport News, Va.) (Boxes 43 and 44)
    Newport News Shipbuilding and Dry Dock Company (Box 49)
  - Williams, Wheeler (Box 57)
  - Wilson, [D.P.?] (Box 57)
  - Wilson, Edith Huntington (Box 57)
  - Wines, James N. (Box 57)
  - Winkelman, [E.?] (Box 57)
  - Wissler, Clark, See American Museum of Natural History (Box 8).
  - Woodlawn Cemetery (Box 57)
  - Woodruff, Timothy L. (Box 57)
  - Work Projects Administration Federal Art Project, See Federal Art Project (Box 32).
  - Worth, Karen (Box 57)
  - Wotring, Sara A. (Box 57)
  - Wright, Edward Hyatt (Box 57)
  - Wright, Frank Cookman (Box 57)
  - Wright, John K. (Box 57)
  - Wykeham-George, Parker, See Hispanic Society of America (Boxes 35-37).
  - W, 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Yale Club (Box 58)
  - Yale University (Box 58)
  - Yarrington family, Archer's mother's family (Box 58)
  - Young, Lewis Ludington (Box 58)
  - Y (Box 58)
  - Zabriskie, George A., See New-York Historical Society (Box 49).
  - Zendegui, Guillermo de (Box 58)
  - Zimmerman, Marie (Box 58)
  - Zubiaurre, Valentin de (Box 58)
  - Zuloaga, Ignacio (Box 58)
  - Z (Box 58)
  - Unidentified letters
    - Family (Box 58)
    - No last name (Box 58)
    - No name (Box 58)
  - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 59)
  - Correspondence records, A-Z, 6 folders (Box 59)
- Financial-legal files
  - Bank statements
    - Bank of New York, 1940; 1942,; 1945-1948,; 1951,; 1953-1956,; 1960-1964; 3 folders (Box 60)
    - Bridgeport City Trust, 1956 (Box 60)
    - City National Bank and Trust of Danbury [Conn.], 1952; 1956,; 1957 (Box 60)
    - Connecticut Bank and Trust, 1956; 1957,; 1962-1966 (Box 60)
    - Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1947-1957; 1959; 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Hanover Bank, 1952-1953; 1955-1962 (Box 60)
    - Hartford National Bank, 1964 (Box 60)
    - Manufacturer's Hanover Trust, 1963-1964 (Box 60)
    - J.P. Morgan Company, 1955-1958; 4 folders (Box 60)
    - J.P. Morgan Company, 1959 (Box 61)
    - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company, 1959-1966; 7 folders (Box 61)
    - State Planters Bank of Commerce and Trusts, 1961-1963 (Box 61)
    - Union and New Haven Trust Company, 1954 (Box 61)
  - Brookgreen (Box 61)
  - Hatzfeldt, Clara (Perkins) (Box 62)
  - Hispanic Society of America, 1957; 1958 (Box 62)
  - Huntington, Archer Milton
    - Trusts and Deeds of Gifts, 1957; summary only, no actual legal documents (Box 62)
    - Will, estate (Box 62)
    - Miscellaneous notes, 3 folders (Box 62)
  - Real estate gifts (Box 62)
  - Receipts, miscellaneous (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous volume (with index), 1891-1940 (Box 62)
  - General
    - 1885, 1891, 1897, 1898 (Box 63)
    - 1904-1906, 1918 (Box 63)
    - 1922-1942, 1945, 1948-1956, 7 folders (Box 63)
    - 1957, Jan-Jun (Box 63)
    - 1957, Jul-Dec (Box 64)
    - 1958-1964, 7 folders (Box 64)
    - 1965-1967, 2 folders (Box 65)
    - Undated (Box 65)
- Memorabilia
  - Address books, 3 folders / 5 volumes (Box 66)
  - Address books, 2 folders / 4 volumes (Box 67)
  - Awards and certificates (Box 67)
    See also Correspondence-subject files: Deerhounds: Awards (Boxes 19-24).
  - Awards and certificates, oversize (Oversize 3)
  - Calendars (daily)
    - 1925, 1930-1937, 9 items (Box 68)
    - 1938-1945, 8 items (Box 69)
    - 1946-1953, 8 items (Box 70)
    - 1954-1961, 8 items (Box 71)
    - 1962-1969, 8 items (Box 72)
    - 1970-1971, 2 items (Box 73)
  - Commemorative postal set (America's First Space Decade), 1971 (Box 73)
  - Diaries
    - 1925-1930, 2 folders / 4 volumes (Box 73)
    - 1931-1942, 6 folders / 12 volumes (Box 74)
    - 1943-1950, 4 folders / 8 volumes (Box 75)
    - 1951-1956, 3 folders / 6 volumes (Box 76)
    - 1957-1962, 3 folders / 6 volumes (Box 77)
    - 1963-1965, 2 folders / 3 volumes (Box 78)
  - Letter pouch (empty) (Box 78)
  - Medals, 2 folders (Box 78)
  - Medals, 3 folders (Box 79)
  - Medals, Hispanic Society of America commemorative medal; unidentified medal; 2 items (Box 86)
  - Medical charts and notes (Box 79)
  - Membership cards (Box 79)
  - Nameplates, 2 items (Box 80)
  - Notes and sketches (Box 80)
  - Passports, for AHH and Archer (Box 80)
  - Pen and Brush Club honorary dinner, 1947 (Box 80)
  - Pistol permits, 1953-1960 (Box 80)
  - Plaques
    - Committee pro Cuba Liberation (Box 80)
    - Danbury Hospital, 1972 (Box 80)
    - Fraternite des Artistes (Box 80)
    - National Wildlife Federation, 1971 (Box 80)
  - Scrapbooks
    - "A very merry Christmas...from Eddie and Peggy Eagan", 1967 (Box 81)
    - "Alpheus Hyatt Fund, Harvard University 1927-1950", 2 folders (Box 81)
    - Antigua (Box 81)
    - Barbados (Box 81)
    - Camp Arbutus, 2 folders (Box 81)
    - Campus Huntington (Box 82)
    - Collis Potter Huntington (Box 82)
    - "La estatua a su paso por Barcelona" (Box 82)
    - Family photos (labeled) (Oversize 4)
      See also Photographs: Family (Boxes 95-97, Oversize 1, 2, 14, 15) for additional family photographs
    - Hispanic Society, 1950; Photographs of buildings, statuary (Oversize 4)
    - Inventory of paintings (Oversize 5)
    - Irving Green, 1967 (Oversize 5)
    - Martinique (Box 82)
    - 90th birthday (Box 82)
    - Peninsula Junior Nature Center and Museum (Oversize 4)
    - Plum Trees School (Box 82)
    - Postcards, miscellaneous collection of postcards (Oversize 4)
    - Sailing (?) trip, 1930; Southern US, Cuba, Puerto Rico, Haiti (Oversize 5)
    - "Espana" (Spain) (Box 83)
    - Stanerigg, 2 volumes (Box 83)
    - Stevens Institute of Technology (Oversize 4)
    - Miscellaneous personal photos (Box 84)
    - Unidentified photos (possibly Brookgreen?) (Oversize 4)
    - Unidentified photos (Box 84)
    - Unidentified (poems, clippings) (Oversize 6)
  - Sculpture tools, wire frames (Box 87)
  - Sculpture tools (Oversize 7)
  - Secretary's diaries
    - 1934, 1936, 1937, 3 volumes (Box 84)
    - 1938-1940, 3 volumes (Box 85)
    - 1945 (Box 84)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Anderson, Maxwell, original poem in praise of AHH's "Diana" (Oversize 3)
    - Benet-Espuny, Jose, original artwork, sketch of Stanerigg, inscribed to AHH (Oversize 3)
    - Binder, green, AHH's name in gold (empty) (Oversize 2)
    - Garcia, Joe, original artwork, inscribed to AHH (Oversize 3)
    - Garcia-Mazas family, vase, inscribed to AHH (Box 86)
    - Glidden, —, original artwork, inscribed to AHH (Oversize 3)
    - Sketch of AHH with her Great Danes, 1896; pen and ink, apparently for magazine cover? (Oversize 3)
    - Sybil Ludington commemorative plate (Box 86)
    - University of South Carolina, honorary degree, including academic regalia (Oversize 2)
    - Valencia (Spain), decree of honorary citizenship, framed (Oversize 2)
    - Miscellaneous, awards, certificates, small artifacts, etc. (unfoldered); includes World War I Red Cross poster (rolled), poster/print of Kaiser Wilhelm II (rolled) (Oversize 3)
- Photographs
  - Artwork by AHH
    AHH frequently gave multiple titles, or no title, to her work. For this reason, all artwork is listed alphabetically by description of the main content. Title(s), if known, are given following the description of the work.
    - Abraham Lincoln (Box 88)
    - Andrew Jackson (Box 88)
    - Angel (1) (Box 88)
    - Angel (2) (Box 88)
    - Arabella Huntington memorial (Box 88)
    - Archer Milton Huntington, bust (Box 88)
    - Base of "The Thinker", base only; statue by another artist (Box 88)
    - Bear with cubs, various (Box 88)
    - Bears, group (Box 88)
    - Bears, various (Box 88)
    - Bears, oversize (Oversize 8)
    - Boabdil, Hispanic Society (Box 88)
    - Boy and crane (Box 88)
    - Boy and fish (Box 88)
    - Boy on seahorse (1), "Sketch for fountain - East Wind" (Box 88)
    - Boy on seahorse (2), "Sketch for fountain - West Wind" (Box 88)
    - Buffalo (Box 88)
    - Bull, head (Box 88)
    - Bull, charging (Box 88)
    - Bulls, fighting (Box 88)
    - Camel with rider, "Ship of the Desert" ? (Box 88)
    - Centaur, baby (Box 88)
    - Centaur, "Centaur Cheiron" (Box 88)
    - Centaur, oversize, "Centaur Cheiron" (Oversize 9)
    - Centaur, female (Box 88)
    - Centaurs, fighting (Box 88)
    - Children, various (Box 88)
    - Children, various oversize (Oversize 12)
    - Collis P. Huntington, bust (Box 88)
    - Collis P. Huntington, statue (Box 88)
    - Collis P. Huntington, memorial (Box 88)
    - Crane, angry, "Angry Crane" (Box 88)
    - Crane and young (Box 88)
    - Cranes rising (Box 88)
    - Deer, doe and fawn (1) (Box 88)
    - Deer, doe and fawn (2) (Box 88)
    - Deer, fawn (Box 88)
    - Deer, fawn scratching (Box 88)
    - Deer, fawns playing (Box 88)
    - Deer, red stag (1) (Box 88)
    - Deer, red stag (2) (Box 88)
    - Deer, red stag, head (Box 88)
    - Deer, red stags fighting (Box 88)
    - Deer runnning (Box 88)
    - Deerhound, "Hound on the hill" (Box 88)
    - Deerhound, head (Box 88)
    - Deerhound, seated (Box 88)
    - Deerhounds, group (Box 88)
    - Diana, "Diana of the Chase," "Young Diana" (Box 88)
    - Dog, head, "Police dog, head" (Box 89)
    - Dog, lying down, "Police dog lying down" (Box 89)
    - Dog, sitting, "Police dog sitting" (Box 89)
    - Don Quixote, 2 folders (Box 89)
    - Don Quixote oversize (Oversize 11)
    - Donkey, bucking (Box 89)
    - Donkey, head (Box 89)
    - Donkey with woman, "Naples" (Box 89)
    - Door panels (Hispanic Society?) (Box 89)
    - Doors, Hispanic Society (Box 89)
    - Duck (Box 89)
    - Ducks (geese?) (Box 89)
    - Eagle, head (Box 89)
    - El Cid, statue (Box 89)
    - El Cid, head (Box 89)
    - Elephant, "Alice" (Box 89)
    - Elephant, running (Box 89)
    - Elephants, fighting (Box 89)
    - Elephants, mother and baby (Box 89)
    - Elephants, various, pair (Box 89)
    - Elephants, various, "Peanuts" (Oversize 9)
    - Elk running (Box 89)
    - Elk stag (Box 89)
    - Faun child with goats (Box 89)
    - Flagpole base (Box 89)
    - Fox and bird (Box 89)
    - Giraffe, mother and baby (Box 89)
    - Goat, head (1) (Box 89)
    - Goat, head (2) (Box 89)
    - Goat, lying down (Box 89)
    - Goat, scratching (Box 89)
    - Goat, standing (Box 89)
    - Goats, fighting (Box 89)
    - Goats, various (Box 89)
    - Goose, head (Box 89)
    - Gorillas, various (Box 89)
    - Great Dane, lying down (1), annotated on back, "Anna Hyatt Huntington, her first sculpture" (Box 89)
    - Great Dane, lying down (2) (Box 89)
    - Great Dane, seated (Box 89)
    - Greyhound, licking self, "Study of Echo" (Box 89)
    - Greyhound, lying down, "Echo lying down" (Box 89)
    - Greyhound, panting, "Speedy" (Box 89)
    - Greyhound, scratching, "Echo scratching" (Box 89)
    - Greyhound, sleeping, "Study of Echo" (Box 89)
    - Greyhound, startled, "Echo startled" (Box 89)
    - Greyhound, with old shoe, "Echo with old shoe" (Box 89)
    - Greyhounds, playing (Box 89)
    - Greyhounds, playing, oversize (Oversize 9)
    - Greyhounds, various (Box 89)
    - Henry P. Davison, bust (Box 90)
    - Hispanic Society, medal (Box 90)
    - Holy family (Box 90)
    - Horse, colt standing (1) (Box 90)
    - Horse, colt standing (2) (Box 90)
    - Horse, colt standing (3), "Six months old" (Box 90)
    - Horse, colt standing (4) (Box 90)
    - Horse, head, Aida (Box 90)
    - Horse, head (1) (Box 90)
    - Horse, head (2) (Box 90)
    - Horse, head (3) (Box 90)
    - Horse, standing (Box 90)
    - Horse and plowman, "L'Orage" (Box 90)
    - Horse with bows, "Rocinante" (Box 90)
    - Horse with wreath, "Victory horse" (Box 90)
    - Horses and chariot (Box 90)
    - Horses, colts playing (Box 90)
    - Horses, fighting, "Stallions fighting" or "Fighting Stallions"; 2 folders (Box 90)
    - Horses, fighting, oversize, "Stallions fighting" or "Fighting Stallions" (Oversize 12)
    - Horses, group, "Colts in storm" (Box 90)
    - Horses, group, "Winter" (Box 90)
    - Horses, mare and foal (Box 90)
    - Horses on wave, "White horses of the sea" (Box 90)